Guide to the Yale Clubs and Societies Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale clubs and societies photographs
1850-1994
RU 692
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
36.5
(33 boxes)
The materials consist of pictures and photographs of the activities and members of Yale clubs, societies, fraternities, vocal groups, and organizations.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 40 (YRG 40), Records of Yale clubs, societies, and organizations.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of pictures and photographs of the activities and members of Yale clubs, societies, fraternities, vocal groups, and organizations.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged alphabetically by organization name.
College students -- Societies, etc.; Greek letter societies; Engravings (prints); Lithographs; Photographs; Slides (photographs); Yale University -- Societies, etc.; Yale University -- Students
- Pictures of clubs, societies, and organizations, Yale University, circa 1850-1994; Series I
  - Clubs, General
    General note
    See also: Oversize
    - Oriental Group of the Cosmopolitan Club, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - WOCD Radio Station, 1942- 1947 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Fraternities, General
    - Inter-fraternity Council, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Various insignia (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified group (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified fraternity house (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Plays
      - "Thanksgiving Jubilee", 1869 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - "Beach of Promise," "Alonzo the Brave", 1876 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - circa 1877 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - "Penikeese", circa 1882 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - "Medea" and Unidentified, 1883 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - 1893 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - "Pirates of Penzance", circa 1895 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - "Ralph Royster Doyster", 1900 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - circa 1910, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Societies, General--Secret Society Buildings, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Alley Cats, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Alpha Chi Sigma, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Alpha Delta Phi
    See also: Oversize, boxes 9-10, folders 329-340
    See also: Folio, Alpha Delta Phi
    - circa 1888-1890 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1892, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1898, 1899, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 1902, 1902?, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 1904, 1905, circa 1907 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 1908, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 1910, circa 1910 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 1911, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 1913, 1914, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - 1916, 1917, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 1919, 1919? (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - 1920, circa 1920, 1922, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 1924, 1925, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 1927, 1928, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 1930, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - 1932, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Alpha Phi Omega, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Apollo Glee Club, circa 1907-1914 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    General
    See also: Oversize, box 10, folder 341
  - Arctic Club
    See also: Oversize, box 10, folder 342
    - Second Annual Dinner, 1895 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Atalanta Boat Club, 1843, 1852, 1861 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Augmented Seven, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Aviation Club
    - 1918, 1928, 1937, 1940, 1941, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Baker's Dozen, 1949, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Banjo and Mandolin Club
    See also: Oversize, box 10, folders 346-349
    - 1887, 1888, 1890 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - 1891, 1892, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - 1895 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - 1912, 1920 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Beaumont Medical Club
    - Tablet Honoring, Dr. Wm. Beaumont, Undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Beethoven Society, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Berzelius, circa 1859, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    See also: Oversize, box 11, folder 350
  - Beta Theta Pi
    See also: Oversize, boxes 11-12, folders 351-357
    - circa 1910, 1911, 1915, circa 1921 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - 1962 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Bible Class, circa 1898 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Book and Bond, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    See also: Oversize box 12, folder 359
  - Book and Snake
    See also: Oversize, box 12, folder 361-362
    - 1863 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - circa 1890 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Budget Drive, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Byers Hall Student Committee, 1920, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Calliopean Society, circa 1930 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Campaign Club (Yale Law School Republicans), 1892 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Canon and Castle, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Centre Espanol, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Chess Club, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    See also: Oversize, box 12, folder 365
  - Chi Phi, 1882, 1892?, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    See also: Oversize box 12, folder 366-367
  - Chi Psi, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Colony
    See also: Oversize, box 12, folder 370
    - Main Room, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Dana Club, 1932, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Delta Kappa Epsilon
    See also: Oversize boxes 13-14, folders 377-381
    - buildings of non-Yale Chapter, undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - circa 1882, 1883 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - 1892, 1905, circa 1960, undated (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Delta Psi (St. Anthony's)
    See also: Oversize box 14, folder 382
    - 1890, 1934, 1962? (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - 1935, 1936 (Folder 28)
  - Depew Battalion, 1889 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    See also: Oversize box 14, folder 383
  - Dramatic Association
    See also: Oversize boxes 14-15, folders 385-389
    - circa 1902 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - "The Pretenders", 1907 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - 1908 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - "The Amazons," "Blackout," Unidentified, circa 1908 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - "The Critic", 1909 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - "London Assurance," and neg, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - members, "Il Ventaglio", 1911 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - "Taming of theShrew," and neg, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - "Movies," neg., "Iphigenia in Taurus," at the Yale Bowl, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - circa 1917? (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - 1921 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - "The Frogs", 1924 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - "Out of Luck", 1925 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - 1930 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - "Julius Caesar,", "Eastward Ho," "Merry-Go-Round", 1932 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - "Wings Over Europe", 1936 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - 1937 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - "1866 and All That", 1938 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - "Trial By Jury", 1939
    - "The Frogs", 1941 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - "Yale Animal", 1953 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - "The Tempest", 1954 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - "Stover at Yale", 1954 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - "Stover at Yale," negs, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - "Skin of Our Teeth", 1958 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - "Henry VI, Part 3," "Mistress of an Inn", 1962 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - circa 1965 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - "Curlew River", 1967 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - "Anything Goes", 1974 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Unidentified (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Duke's Men, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Dwight Hall, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Eating Clubs
    - 1864, 1867, 1869, 1870, circa 1870, 1879, 1883, 1885, 1886 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - 1888, circa 1890, 1893, 1896, 1897, 1905, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Elihu Club, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Elizabethan Club
    - circa 1918, 1938, 1941, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - undated (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Eta Phi, 1890 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    See also: Oversize box 15, folder 391
  - Fence Club, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    See also: Oversize boxes 15-18, folders 392-416
  - Film Society, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Financial Union, officers, 1900 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Franklin Hall, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Fraternal Order of Bachelors, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Freshman Chorus, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Class of 1960 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Game Club, circa 1881 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Gamma Nu, Insignia, 1855 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Glee, Banjo, and Mandolin Club (Box 4, Folder 112)
    See also: Oversize box 19, folder 423-425
    - 1888, 1896, 1906, 1908, 1911, 1952
  - Glee Club
    See also: Oversize and Folio
    - 1863 (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - 1875, 1877 (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - 1879, 1883 (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - 1884, 1885 (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - 1886,1987 (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - 1888, 1889 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - 1890, circa 1890, 1892 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - 1896, 1898 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - 1913, 1913 (individuals-Cole Porter), (1915?), 1917, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - 1931, 1931, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - 1933, 1934, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - 1937, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - 1940, 1941, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - circa 1950, 1953, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - World Tour, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - undated (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Halcyon Boat Club, 1854, undated (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - He Boule (Box 5, Folder 130)
    See also: Oversize box 20, folders 426-427
    - Members in theatrical costumes, circa 1900 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Hillhouse Gang, circa 1884 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - The Hogans
    - 1903, 1905, 1906, 1907 (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - 1908, 1909, 1910, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - 1912, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - 1914, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - The Jesters, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - Kappa Beta Phi, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Kappa Psi, 1899, 1900 (Box 6, Folder 139)
    See also: Oversize box 20, folder 429
  - Kappa Sigma Epsilon
    - 1840 (Box 6, Folder 140)
    - 1870 (Box 6, Folder 140)
    - insignia, undated (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Knights of the Round Table, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - Kopper Kettle Klub, 1907 (Box 6, Folder 142)
    See also: Oversize box 20, folder 430
  - Liberal Club, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 143)
    See also: Oversize box 20, folder 431
  - Molly Coddles, 1908 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - More House Choir (St. Thomas More Church), 1962 (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - Mory's
    See also: Oversize box 20, folders 434-435
    - circa 1912 (Box 6, Folder 146)
    - Temple St., pre-1912 (Box 6, Folder 146)
    - Thornton Wilder, W.L. Phelps, and others, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 146)
    - Presentation of the cup, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 146)
    - Velvet Cup, circa 1888 (Box 6, Folder 147)
    - Cupmen, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 147)
    - a singing group?, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 148)
    - 1970 (Box 6, Folder 148)
    - 1972 (Box 6, Folder 148)
    - Misc. (Including Mr. and Mrs. Moriarty and Unidentified groups) (Box 6, Folder 148)
  - Olympia Boat Club, 1857, 1858 (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - Orchestra, 1887, undated (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - Our Boarding Club, 1879 (Box 6, Folder 151)
  - Phi Beta Kappa
    - Key, 1832 (Box 6, Folder 152)
    - Key, 1868 (Box 6, Folder 152)
    - 1902 (Box 6, Folder 153)
    - 1936, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 153)
    - 1937 (Box 6, Folder 153)
  - Phi Delta Phi (Yale Law School), 1890 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Phi Gamma Delta, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 155)
  - Pictorial Board, 1931, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - Psi Upsilon
    See also: Oversize box 20-21, folder 436-439
    - circa 1881, 1890, 1891 (Box 6, Folder 157)
  - Pundits
    See also: Oversize box 21, folder 440
    - 1938, 1941, 1943, undated (Box 6, Folder 158)
  - Republican Club, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 159)
  - Rifle Club, 1921 (Box 6, Folder 160)
  - St. Elmo's, 1935?, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 161)
    See also: Oversize box 21, folder 442
  - Scroll and Key, 1864, 1866 (Box 6, Folder 162)
    See also: Oversize box 21, folder 444
  - Sigma Xi, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 163)
  - Skull and Bones
    See also: Oversize box 22, folder 449-450
    - 1861, 1868, 1871 (Box 6, Folder 164)
    - 1873, circa 1878 (Box 6, Folder 165)
    - photos of bones, undated (Box 6, Folder 165)
    - 1948 (Box 6, Folder 166)
    - General, undated (Box 6, Folder 166)
    - 1954 (Box 27)
    - 1955 (Box 27)
    - 1956 (Box 27)
    - 1957 (Box 27)
    - 1958 (Box 27)
    - 1961 (Box 27)
    - 1962 (Box 27)
  - Society of Orpheus and Bacchus, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 167)
  - Sports Car Club, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 168)
  - Student Council, 1928- 1932 (Box 6, Folder 169)
  - Tau Beta Pi, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 170)
  - Thimble and Corkers, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 171)
  - Thulia Boat Club, 1854 (Box 6, Folder 172)
  - Torch Honor Society, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 173)
    See also: Oversize box 22, folder 454-458
  - University Choir (Battell Chapel), 1936, 1938, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 174)
  - University Quartet, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 175)
  - Varuna Boat Club, 1861? (Box 7, Folder 176)
  - Volunteer Band, 1891-1921 (Box 7, Folder 177)
  - WYBC, 1962, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 178)
  - Wesley Foundation, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 179)
  - Whiffenpoofs
    See also: Oversize box 23, folder 462-463
    - 1910, 1912, 1913, circa 1913?, 1914 (Box 7, Folder 180)
    - 1915, 1917 (Box 7, Folder 180)
    - 1925, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 181)
    - (text about members), 1937 (Box 7, Folder 181)
    - 1938 (Box 7, Folder 181)
    - 30th Anniversary, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 182)
    - 1942, 1949, 1962, 1977, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 183)
    - undated (Box 7, Folder 184)
  - Wolf's Head, 1886 (Box 7, Folder 185)
  - Wooden Spoon
    See also: Oversize box 23, folder 465-466
    - Cochleaurati ("Spoon Graduates")
      - 1865, 1866 (Box 7, Folder 186)
      - 1867, 1868 (Box 7, Folder 187)
      - 1869, undated (Box 7, Folder 188)
    - Coat of Arms (Box 7, Folder 188)
    - Laurence Hall spoon (Box 7, Folder 188)
  - Wurts Debating Club, 1897 (Box 7, Folder 189)
  - Yale Band
    See also: Oversize box 10, folder 345
    - circa 1870?, 1895 (Box 7, Folder 190)
    - 1902, 1934, circa 1935 (Box 7, Folder 191)
    - 1936 (Box 7, Folder 192)
    - 1938, undated (Box 7, Folder 193)
  - Yale Corinthian Yacht Club, 1944, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 194)
  - Yale Debating Association
    See also: Oversize box 13, folder 375
    - 1896, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 195)
    - 1934, 1935, circa 1936, 1950, circa 1960 (Box 7, Folder 196)
    - undated (Box 7, Folder 197)
  - Yale Outing Club, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 198)
  - Yale Political Union
    - 1936, 1938, undated (Box 7, Folder 199)
    - circa 1967 (Box 7, Folder 199)
  - Yale Precision Marching Band, 1969, undated (Box 7, Folder 200)
  - Yale Union Club, 1902 (Box 7, Folder 201)
  - Yale University Club, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 202)
  - Yale University Women's Organization (picnic), circa 1981 (Box 8, Folder 203)
  - Zeta Psi
    - 1892, 1894, 1895 (Box 8, Folder 204)
    - 1896, circa 1900, 1902 (Box 8, Folder 205)
    - circa 1907, circa 1908 (Box 8, Folder 206)
    - 1909 (Box 8, Folder 207)
    - 1910, 1913 (Box 8, Folder 208)
    - 1928, circa 1960, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 209)
  - Miscellaneous, Unidentified (Box 8, Folder 210)
- Oversize, Series II
  - Alpha Delta Phi
    - circa 1888, 1895, 1897 (Box 9, Folder 329)
    - 1900, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 330)
    - 1904, 1905, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 331)
    - 1907, 1908 (Box 9, Folder 332)
    - Cast of play, 1909 (Box 9, Folder 333)
    - 1909 (Box 9, Folder 334)
    - 1910 (Box 9, Folder 335)
    - 1911 (Box 10, Folder 336)
    - 1916, circa 1920, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 337)
    - circa 1926, circa 1928 (Box 10, Folder 338)
    - 1930, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 339)
    - undated (Box 10, Folder 340)
  - Apollo Glee Club, circa 1900-1905 (Box 10, Folder 341)
  - Arctic Club, 1894 (Box 10, Folder 342)
  - Arctic Club, North Pole, 1909-1910 (Box 10, Folder 343)
  - Aurelians (Sheffield Scientific School), 1934 (Box 10, Folder 344)
  - Yale Band, 1931-1933 (Box 10, Folder 345)
  - Banjo and Mandolin Club
    - 1890-1893 (Box 10, Folder 346)
    - 1897, circa 1896, circa 1900 (Box 10, Folder 347)
    - circa 1908 (Box 10, Folder 348)
    - undated (Box 11, Folder 349)
  - Berzelius, 1858(?), 1879, circa 1880, 1896, circa 1900 (Box 11, Folder 350)
  - Beta Theta Pi
    - Theatrical, circa 1903-1907 (Box 11, Folder 351)
    - 1907, 1908 (Box 11, Folder 352)
    - 1909, 1910, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 353)
    - 1912, 1913 (Box 11, Folder 354)
    - Phi Chi Chapter, 1913 April (Box 11, Folder 355)
    - Phi Chi Chapter, 1913 May (Box 12, Folder 356)
    - Undated (Box 12, Folder 357)
  - Black Bull, 1901 (Box 12, Folder 358)
  - Book and Bond Society, 1900, 1901, 1943S (Box 12, Folder 359)
  - Book and Gavel Society, 1898-99, 1899-1900 (Box 12, Folder 360)
  - Book and Snake
    - 1888, 1897, 1897S (Box 12, Folder 361)
    - 1964 (Box 12, Folder 362)
  - The Byron Club, 1909 (Box 12, Folder 363)
  - The New Haven Camera Club, 1909 (Box 12, Folder 364)
  - The Chess Club, 1911, 1913 (Box 12, Folder 365)
  - Chi Phi
    - 1893, circa 1900, 1920, circa 1940 (Box 12, Folder 366)
    - 1934 (Box 12, Folder 367)
  - The Chinese Student Club, 1916-1917 (Box 12, Folder 368)
  - Cinema Association, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 369)
  - Colony Association, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 370)
  - Corbey Court
    - 1897, 1899 (Box 13, Folder 371)
    - 1911, 1912, 1913 (Box 13, Folder 372)
  - St. Paul's Cricket Team (Box 13, Folder 373)
  - Yale Deacons, 1931,1932 (Box 13, Folder 374)
  - Yale Debating Association, 1931, 1932, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 375)
  - Delta Epsilon Ipsilon, circa 1900 (Box 13, Folder 376)
  - Delta Kappa Epsilon
    See also: Psi Upsilon, 1914 box 21, folder 438
    - 1891, 1892, 1893 (Box 13, Folder 377)
    - 1894, 1895, 1902, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 378)
    - 1904, 1905, circa 1907 (Box 14, Folder 379)
    - 1910, 1936, circa 1942, 1944, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 380)
    - 1943, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 381)
  - Delta Psi, 1893-94, 1894-1895, 1896-1897, 1899, 1934S (Box 14, Folder 382)
  - Depew Battalion, 1889 (Box 14, Folder 383)
  - Yale Dining Club, 1907 (Box 14, Folder 384)
  - Dramatic Association
    - 1896, 1902, 1909, 1914 (Box 14, Folder 385)
    - circa 1900, 1906-1907, 1907-1908, 1908-1909 (Box 14, Folder 386)
    - "The Critic", circa 1908-1909 (Box 14, Folder 387)
    - 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 388)
    - undated (Box 15, Folder 389)
  - The Elihu Club Delegation, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 390)
  - Eta Phi, 1893 (Box 15, Folder 391)
  - Fence Club
    - 1890, circa 1891, 1892, 1895 (Box 15, Folder 392)
    - 1895, 1896, 1899-1900, circa 1900 (Box 15, Folder 393)
    - 1900, 1901, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 394)
    - Psi Upsilon, 1902 (Box 15, Folder 395)
    - 1904, 1905, 1906 (Box 15, Folder 396)
    - 1907, 1908 (Box 16, Folder 397)
    - 1909 (Box 16, Folder 398)
    - 1910, 1911 (Box 16, Folder 399)
    - 1912, 1913 (Box 16, Folder 400)
    - 1912 (Box 16, Folder 401)
    - 1914, 1915, 1916 (Box 17, Folder 402)
    - 1917, 1918, 1919, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 403)
    - 1921, 1922, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 404)
    - 1926, 1927, 1928, 1929 (Box 17, Folder 405)
    - 1931, 1932 (Box 17, Folder 406)
    - 1934, 1935, 1937, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 407)
    - 1941, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 408)
    - 1944 (Box 17, Folder 409)
    - 1945 n, 1947 n, 1947 n, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 410)
    - 1949, 1949 m, 1950 f, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 411)
    - 1953, 1954, 1958, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 412)
    - Undated (Box 18, Folder 413-416)
  - Glee Club
    - 1882, 1883 (Box 18, Folder 417)
    - 1889-1890 (Box 18, Folder 418)
    - 1890, 1891, 1892 (Box 19, Folder 419)
    - 1902, 1910, 1911 (Box 19, Folder 420)
    - circa 1903-1907 (Box 19, Folder 421)
    - 1931, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 422)
  - Glee, Banjo, and Mandolin Club
    - 1895, circa 1900, circa 1901, circa 1902 (Box 19, Folder 423)
    - 1903, 1904, 1905, 1906 (Box 19, Folder 424)
    - 1908, 1910, 1911-1912 (Box 19, Folder 425)
  - He' Boule
    - circa 1892, circa 1893 (Box 20, Folder 426)
    - circa 1895 (Box 20, Folder 427)
  - Junior Prom Committee, 1916 (Box 20, Folder 428)
  - Kappa Psi, 1895-96 (Box 20, Folder 429)
  - Kopper Kettle Klub, 1907 (Box 20, Folder 430)
  - Liberal Club, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 431)
  - Lotus Eaters, 1880, 1877 (Box 20, Folder 432)
  - Mohicans, 1912, 1915 (Box 20, Folder 433)
  - Mory's
    - 1938, 1940, 1946, 1967, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 434)
    - Cup Presentation?, circa 1940s (Box 20, Folder 435)
  - Psi Upsilon
    - 1890, 1891, 1893, 1894 (Box 20, Folder 436)
    - circa 1894, circa 1896, 1897, 1899, 1900 (Box 20, Folder 437)
    - 1900, 1908, 1909, 1914, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 438)
    - 1921, 1923, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 439)
  - Pundits, 1917, 1943, 1944, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 440)
  - Sachem 1934S (Box 21, Folder 441)
  - St. Elmo's
    - Dance, Circa 1927 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - 1934S (Box 21, Folder 442)
  - Scroll and Compass 1934S (Box 21, Folder 443)
  - Scroll and Key, 1869-1870, 1873, 1876, 1895, 1907 (Box 21, Folder 444)
  - Second Glee Club, 1894 (Box 21, Folder 445)
  - The Selects, 1909 (Box 21, Folder 446)
  - Senior Suffragettes Club, 1900 (Box 21, Folder 447)
  - Sigma Psi, 1889-1890, 1934S (Box 21, Folder 448)
  - Skull and Bones
    - 1884, 1887, 1888, 1900, 1901, 1904 (Box 22, Folder 449)
    - circa 1890, 1892 (Box 22, Folder 450)
  - Student Council, 1915-16 (Box 22, Folder 451)
  - Swiss Marines, 1917, 1919 (Box 22, Folder 452)
  - Theta Xi, 1888 (Box 22, Folder 453)
  - Torch Honor Society Group Pictures
    - 1919, 1925, 1927-1932 (Box 22, Folder 454)
    - 1933-1942 (Box 22, Folder 455)
    - 1942-1943, 1944-1946 (Box 22, Folder 456)
    - 1949-50, 1952, 1956, undated (Box 22, Folder 457)
    - 1955, circa 1960 (Box 22, Folder 458)
  - University Quartet, 1931, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 459)
  - Vernon Seniors, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 460)
  - Volunteer Band, 1898, 1900, 1914 (Box 23, Folder 461)
  - Whiffenpoofs
    - 1912, 1914, 1917, Undated (Box 23, Folder 462)
    - circa 1918, circa 1919, 1931, 1932, 1935, circa 1942 (Box 23, Folder 463)
  - Whitewashers, Circa 1940 (Box 23, Folder 463a)
  - Wolf's Head Alumni Dinner, circa 1900-class of circa 1887 (Box 23, Folder 464)
  - Wooden Spoon
    - Coghlauriati, 1863 (Box 23, Folder 465)
    - 1869 ('70) (Box 23, Folder 466)
  - York Hall, 1934 (Box 23, Folder 467)
  - Zeta Psi
    - 1893, 1884, 1895 (Box 23, Folder 468)
    - circa 1899, circa 1900, 1900, 1901(?) (Box 23, Folder 469)
    - 1903, 1904, 1905, circa 1906 (Box 24, Folder 470)
    - 1907, 1908, 1910 (Box 24, Folder 471)
    - 1908 (Box 24, Folder 472)
    - 1911, 1912 (Box 24, Folder 473)
    - 1913, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 474)
    - 1922, circa 1923, 1924 (Box 24, Folder 475)
  - Miscellaneous Unidentified (Box 25, Folder 476-477)
  - Miscellaneous Unidentified (Box 25, Folder 478-480)
  - Miscellaneous Unidentified (Box 26, Folder 481-487)
  - Slides
    - Glee Club (Box 30)
    - Whiffenpoofs (Box 31)
- Folio, Series III
  - Alpha Delta Phi
    - 1894 (Box DR17F58)
    - 81st Annual Convention, 1913 (Box DR17F58)
  - Delta Epsilon Iota, 1920-1921 (Box DR17F58)
  - Glee Club
    - In Washington DC, 1926 (Box DR17F58)
    - 1938 (Box DR17F58)
  - Skel-Eton club banner, 1863 (Box DR32F100)
  - Zeta Psi
    - of North America, in Boston, 1913 (Box DR17F58)
    - German at Waldorf Astoria, 1913 (Box DR17F58)
    - 95th Convention Banquet, 1943 (Box DR17F58)
  - Miscellaneous, Unidentified (Box DR17F58)
  - William Graham Sumner Club, 1940-10-31 (Box DR32F100)
    Scope and Contents
    Dinner at the Yale Club for the 100th anniversary of Sumner's birth